You must be Senator Beriam's wife, right?
The order has changed.
Is that liquor?
Is that box really that precious to you?
There's but one method to prevent Rail Tracer from coming.
いや あの そのさ えと
え 何て言うか
How should I put it...
あれだよ ほら
平和的にさ 解決しようよ ね?
You know, that...
Let's settle this in a peaceful manner.
Okay?
It's all right.
大丈夫
僕たちならできるよ ね?
We can do this.
Okay?
だからだからさ その銃をさ
下ろしてよお ね ね?
That's why... That's why... you have to lower your guns.
Okay? Okay?
頼むよ ほんとに怖いんだ
Please!
It's really scary!
でもお金は今 一銭も持ってないんで
とりあえず謝るから…
I don't even have a dime on me right now,
so I'll just apologize for now.
Lower your guns, please.
銃を下ろして…
下ろしてよおおお!
Lower them!
Hey...
おい 本当にこいつで
間違いないのか
Is this really the one?
そのはずです
He ought to be.
Having a tattoo of a sword on your face...
ぃゎすみ
顔に剣の刺青なんて
間違いようがありません
There's no way to mistake that.
But he's just too pathetic.
それにしても情けなさすきるぜ
おい
Hey.
な 何?
What?
まず泣くのをやめろ
First, stop your crying.
な 泣いてなんかないよ
I-I'm not...
...crying.
You surely are crying.
泣いてるじやねえか
I'm not crying, I tell you!
泣いてなんかないつてばぁ !
ハア もういい
Enough already.
う うゎあ‥ うう‥
Get this.
いいか?
If you don't want a hole in your head, say your name.
頭に風穴開けられたくなけりゃ
お前の名前を言え
《 繁 《《
シ ソ ソソ'
J-J-Ja—
ゆつくり… はつきりとだ
Slowly and clearly.
ジヤ ジヤグジ一…
ジヤグジ一スプロッ 卜 !
J-Jacuzzi... Jacuzzi Splot!
来たんだ…
遅かつたんだ…
It's here!
We were too late!
もう追いついちゃったんだ
It's already caught up!
レイル卜レ一サ一…
Rail Tracer!
No way.
ウソ‥
What on earth is this?
何なの これ?
ぬあ
Nice... Donny!
二一ス ド二一…
良かつた 無事だったんだね
That's a relief.
You were all right.
I'm so relieved.
良かつた 本当に良かつた…
Really relieved.
私たちは何 とかね
We managed somehow;
けど二ックは
黒服の連中に捕まった
However, Nick was caught by the people in black suits.
大変だああぁ
It's terrible!
ヤバいよ ヤバいよ うおっ
It's dangerous, dangerous!
You remember there was a black-suit orchestra, right?
黒服の楽団がいたでしょ?
あいつら 列車強盗だつ たみたい
It seems they are train robbers.
We'll definitely go and save Nick later.
二ツクはあとで必ず助け出すから…
それより これはどういうことなの ?
What happened here though?
そうだよ 大変なんだよ
That's right! It's terrible!
Rail Tracer...
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一カヾ
レイ 丿し卜レ一サ一が来ちやつたんだ
Rail Tracer has come!
早くここから逃げないと
僕たちも消されちゃう!
If we don't run soon, we'll be erased, too!
So we have to save Nick somehow—
だから二ツクを何とガ助けて…
発砲してる?
Gunfire?
W-What's that?
な 何なの? 今の銃声は何?
Where's that gunfire coming from?!
What are they shooting at?
何を撃つ たの ? 誰か死んだの ?
Did someone die?
Tell me, tell me!
Nice! Donny!
We have to run!
逃げなきや… 早く逃げなきや !
We have to run, quickly!
俺たちルッソファ三リ一を さんざん
手こずらせてくれた不良どものボスが
To think the boss of the delinquents who caused so many problems for the Russo family would be such a coward...
てめえのような臆病者とはなぁ
Makes one laugh, doesn't it?
気の抜ける話じゃねえか
この野郎!
You bastard!
うつ! うう
さんざん俺たちのシマを
荒らしてるつてえから
I was wondering what kind of bad ass you would be...
どんなすげぇ奴かと思えや よお…
since I heard you were ravaging our turf, but...
ぐはつ
た… 確かに僕たちは…
悪党だよ
We are indeed villains;
ケツ !
だけど だけど
最初に酒を売った… ぐふっ
However... However, the ones who started—
The ones who killed no less than eight of my friends—
僕たちの仲間を
8人も殺したのは… ぐわっ
お前たちじゃないか… うわつ
Were you guys!
当然の成り行きだろうが !
That was the natural course of things!
うつ… だから だから決めたんだ
That's why, that's why we decided...
ルツソフアミリ一には うつ…
to radically oppose the Russo family.
徹底的!こぁ攪ガつてやるつて !
Stop your spineless whining!
ガ夕ガ夕ぬかしてるんじやね工 !
でも僕たちが逃げたら…
みんな
But if we run...
Everyone will...
Mr. Isaac, Ms. Miria, Mary, Czes...
All of them will...
ぼ 僕たちで その黒い奴らも
レイ 丿し卜レ一サ一も追い払おう
Let's drive those guys in the black suits and Rail Tracer off!
Jacuzzi...
ジヤグジ一…
やっつけよう 僕たちでそいつらを
Let's drive 'em off!
Okay.
や やめてよお
早く銃を下ろしてよお!
Stop it.
Quickly lower your guns!
な なるベくなら
殺したくないんだよお!
I don't want to kill you!
殺されたくないだろうが!?
You mean you don't want to be killed, right?!
達うよお 殺したくないんだよお !
No, you're wrong! I don't want to kill you!
だから ド二一 まだ待ってあげてよ
頼むよ
So Donny, please wait a little longer!
Please!
この人たちは きつと
銃を下ろしてくれるよおお
These people will definitely lower their guns!
てめえ 何言つて
What the hell are you—
ぬあっ‥
ううつ…
What are you doing?!
お前ら 何してる!
さつさと撃て! 撃ち殺せ!
Shoot him!
Kill him!
うひい !
ご機嫌いかがですか ?
How are you today?
ぬあ‥
わぁ一一一
逃けてええ~~…
Run!
だから言ったじゃないかあぁ~~~~
I warned you!
You...
あんた
バ一ンズさん
Mr. Barnes.
工二ス… なぜ殺さなかつた?
Ennis... Why didn't you kill him?
はい…
Yes, I thought it wouldn't be too late to kill him after he told us what happened...
何が起こつたのか確認してからでも
遅くないと者えたからです
奇弁を壽すな
Don't think!
お前は私が造つたホムンクルスだ
You are a homunculus I created.
You ought to be able to kill others without a trace of hesitation.
何の ためらいもなく
他人を殺せるはず
Gentlemen,
諸君 哀れなバ一ンズを見たまえ
take a look at poor Barnes.
この男が なぜ火事を起こしたのか
完成品の薬をどうしたのか
Why has this guy caused a fire to erupt?
What he has done with the completed medicine?
諸君を老いの恐怖から解放するはずだった
あの薬をなくした男に
Are we going to give this guy, who lost the medicine that was supposed to take your fear of aging away,
弁解の余地を与えるのか ?
a chance to explain himself?
私はイヤだ
I don't want to,
だが完成品の行方は
突き止めなければならぬ
but we have to know what happened to the finished product.
How should I go about this?
どうすればよいか?
There is one method.
ーつだけ方法がある
諸君も よく知つている方法だ
It's a method you gentlemen are familiar with as well.
Used to make Barnes' memories mine...
バ一ンズの知識 バ一ンズの経験
Barnes' knowledge... Barnes' experiences... Barnes' life—
バ一ンズの人生すベてを
我がものにしてしまう方法が
M-Master Szilard...
セ セラ一ド様
こうするのだ !
You do it like this!
ぬゎあ
諸君 喜ぴたまえ
Gentlemen, rejoice!
バ一ンズは火災現場から
2本の完成品を
Barnes managed to save two bottles of the finished product from the fire.
持ち出すことに成功したようだ
奪われたようだがな
It seems the bottles were taken from him though...
そんなあ
奪った連中の顔は分かった
運が良ければ取り戻せるだろう
I know the faces of those who took it.
With some luck, we should be able to recover them.
Ennis.
工二ス
はい
Yes?
Apparently there's a guy who was looking for you, too.
お前を捜している男も
いるようだぞ
今 教えてやろう
I'll show you now.
工二ス
はい
Ennis.
Yes?
まずは その4人組を捜せ
First, go and look for those four guys.
はい
Understood.
Yes... Yes...
はい… はい… それはもぅ
八方手を尽くしておりますが…
We're leaving no stones unturned in our search, but...
はい… 申し訳ございません~
Yes... I'm so sorry...
一刻も早く捜し出せと
言ったはずだ…
I thought I told you to find him as fast as possible?
If you can't find Dallas Genoard, consider your life forfeit.
ダラスジ工ノア一ドが見つからなけれは
お前は自分の首を絞めることになる
Without fail... Without fail I will find him and bring him before you.
必ず 必ず見つけ出して
ご覧に入れます!
ロだけでないことを祈るぞ
I'm praying that it won't be just words...
Idiots!
バ力野郎 !
てめえらが頼りにならねえガら
俺の顔がつぷれるんだろうカヾ!
Since I can't count on you, I'm looking bad!
例の新聞社は!?
What happened to the newspaper company?!
They said they only had ambiguous information concerning Dallas Genoard.
ダラス'ジエノア一ドに関しては
靄睦な情報しかなLと
曖昧だと!?
Ambiguous, you say?
They said they would only sell us that information...
そんな情報しか
売ってもらえませんで…
俺が行く
I'm going there.
てめえらだから
たかヵヾ新聞屋になめられるんだ
The newspaper company looked down on you, because you are nothing but lackeys.
That shitty newspaper company,
クソ新聞社め
絶対 何か隠してやがる
they must be hiding something.
He's an incompetent guy,
無能な男です
使い捨てるにはちょうどいい
a perfect, disposable underling.
くれぐれも穏便な
Be sure to keep this matter silent.
However, how did a lowly juvenile delinquent obtain immortal flesh?
しかし たかヵヾ不良少年が
なぜ不死の肉体に…
未完成品を与えられたそうだ
Apparently he got his hands on an incomplete product.
肉体的な損傷の影響は受けないが
老いに は
He'll be invulnerable to wounds, but...
against aging...
勝てない…
He can't win...
つまり不老ではない と
In other words, he isn't immortal?
我クが追い求めているのは
複雑怪奇で いかがわしく
What we are aiming for is complex, mysterious and questionable,
しかし この手にできれは
かつてない幸福が約束されるものだ
but if we can obtain it, never before seen happiness will be within our grasp.
そのためならば
I wouldn't mind losing my human heart for something like that.
私は人の心をなく しても構ゎん
ヒユ一イ'ラフオレツ卜は
獄の中だ
Huey Laforet is in jail.
You should be able to beat him now.
今なら奴を出し抜ける
I've been so busy...
もう大変なのよぉ
Firo Prochainezo.
フイ一ロブロシ工ンツオ
お前は これから下す問いに
ウソ偽りなく答えることができるか?
Will you be able to answer truthfully to the questions I'm about to ask you?
はい
Yes.
お前は力モッリス夕になることを
望むか?
Do you wish to become a Camorrista?
はい
Yes.
我々力モッラは遠い祖国
イ夕リアの監獄で生まれた組織だ
The Camorra is an organization that was created in a prison in our faraway mother country Italy.
ここから先に足を踏み入れるならば
If you continue down this road, it will sometimes happen that you will have to go to prison and lose your freedom.
時には牢獄に
自由を奪ゎれることもある
理不尽とも言える闘いの果てに
命を落とすこともあるだろう
It is also possible that you will lose your life at the end of a fight with someone whom you once called a friend.
それを理解しているか?
Do you understand?
はい
Yes.
お前の右足は監獄の中に
左足は鵠輻の中にある
Your right foot stands in prison, and your left foot stands in a coffin.
それでもお前は
その目で自らの道を見据え
Even so will you be able to fix your eyes on the road ahead and achieve glory with your right hand?
はい
Yes.
我らのために必要とあらは
己の命を左手で消すことができるか?
If it proves necessary, will you be able to end your life with your left hand?
はい
Yes.
お前の父が我らの仲間を殺した時
If your father kills our friends, will you be able to kill your father and exact revenge for our friends?
お前は父を殺し 伸間の3晨し豊うを
果たすことができるか?
はい
Yes.
フイ一ロ
Firo...
今ならまだ引き返せる
You can still turn back now!
今まで使われる存在だつたお前が
人を使う側に回る
From being one who is being used, you can turn to someone who uses people instead.
この裏社会の
ほんの一部にすきないが
Even though it is only a small bit of the underworld, you will be moving one of the cogs here.
その歯車を
お前が動かすことになる
そうしたら もう後戻りはできない
If you do so, you won't be able to turn back.
正直な話 俺はお前なら
Truthfully, I believe you'd do just fine on a straight path.
表の道でも十分
うまくやつていけると思つている
それだけの力がお前にはある
You have that much strength.
フイ一ロプロシ工ンツォ
Firo Prochainezo,
それでもお前は
この道に足を踏み入れるのか?
will you go down this road even so?
Yes.
はい 覚悟の上です
I am more than prepared.
そうか ならば
その覚悟を見せてみろ
I see.
We'll have you show your preparedness then.
Okay!
よし ジヤグジ一を捜しに行くぞ!
Let's go look for Jacuzzi!
出発だね !
We're leaving, right?!
We're gonna look for Nice, too!
二一スも捜すんだ !
レスキユ一だね !
It's a rescue, right?!
I don't really have a clue what's going on, but...
何だか さつぱり分からないけど
Black-suits... White-suits... Some knife wielding weirdo...
黒服とか 白服とか
ナイフを持つた変な奴とか !
そんなのは この俺の拳銃で脅して
そのスキに逃げてやる
I'll intimidate 'em a little with my pistol,
and run away when they're off guard!
すつごお~い!
Amazing!
いいこと メリ一 チ工ス君と
一緒に静かに隠れていなさい
Listen carefully, Mary.
Go and hide with Czes.
大丈夫よ
It's all right.
明日になれは きっとお父様が
助けに来てくれますからね
Father will surely come to our rescue tomorrow.
Yes...
Czes...
チ工ス君 メ ー丿 一をお願いしますね
Please take good care of Mary.
Okay.
行こう
Let's go.
It is nice meeting you.
ご機嫌うるわしゅう
ベリアム上院議員夫人ですな?
You are Senator Beriam's wife, right?
My name is Goose.
私の名はグ一スと申します
あなたのご主人に折り入って
ご協力 頂きたいことがありましてね
I have a special favor of your husband in which I need your help.
May I ask you to come with me?
ご一緒 頂けますかな
Promise me you won't hurt any of the other passengers.
ほかの乗客の皆さんに
手を出さないと約束して下さい
それはあなたのご主人と
政府の返答次第でしょうな
That will depend on the response of your husband and the government.
Welcome!
いらつしゃいませぇ!
聞きたいことがある
I want to ask you something.
これはこれはルノラ一夕ファミリ一の
グス夕一ヴオ様
Well, well. If it isn't Gustavo of the Runorata family.
幹部自らお越しとは
光栄の至りです
To have the executive himself come over, I am honored.
俺が誰だか分かつているのか
You know who I am?
はい 私どもに
分からないことはございません
Yeees. For us, there is nothing we don't know.
なら話は早い
Then let's cut to the chase.
It seems you made quite the fools out of my subordinates.
うちの若い連中に
なめた態度をとつてくれたそうだな?
なめた態度 ? とんでも ない !
Made fools out of them?
That is ridiculous.
私どもは常に全身全霊をもって
お客様にサ一ビスを…
With complete devotion we always accommodate our customers with the best service—
ジ工ノア一ドのクソガキの行方を
素直に教えねえか!
Tell me where that snotty brat Dallas Genoard is!
W-Wait a—
ちよ ちよつとお待ち…
If you wanna live long, tell me what you know!
早死にしたくねえなら
知つてることを言え!
I'll tell you. I'll tell you, so let go of me.
言います 言いますから放して !
俺を怒らせるな
Don't upset me.
So tell me!
さあ 言え
ダラスジ工ノア一ドはどこにいる?
Where is Dallas Genoard?!
こないだ部下の方にお話した以上のことは
分からないんですよ…
We don't know any more than what we told your subordinates the other day.
Now, if it concerns information surrounding him, it's not like there's no information at all.
ただし周辺情報でしたら
なくもありません
何でもいいから教えねえか !
Just tell me already!
ガンド一ルファミリ一もまた
ダラスを追つています
The Gandor family is after Dallas as well.
ガン ド一ル力ヾ!?
The Gandors?
Why would they, I wonder... hmm?
どうしてでしようねえ…
ん? 先にガン ド一丿しカヾダラスを
見つけたら 何かマズいことでも?
Would it be bad for you if they found him first?
う ガン ド一ルを
出し抜く方法を教えろ
Tell me how to beat the Gandors to the chase.
ダラスジ工 ノア一 ドには
妹がいます
Dallas Genoard has a little sister.
あの ろくでなしにしては
かなり大事にしてる妹がね
For being such a good-for-nothing, he sure takes good care of her.
And?
Don't you think she's the perfect bait to catch Dallas?
ダラスを釣るには
格好の工サじゃありませんか?
互いに ゎだかま り はないな ?
There are no ill feelings between the two of you, right?
もし相手の胸を刺したら
わしがその場で刺したほうを殺すが
If one of you stabs the other in the chest, I will kill the culprit then and there.
Do the two of you understand?
よいな ? 2人とも
Well then, begin!
では… 始めるがよい
皆さん 勝負ありです
Everyone, the match is over.
おお一一つ
はつ はあ!
すごいじやねえか フイ一ロ !
That was amazing, Firo!
あのマイザ一から
一本取つちまうなんてよ!
To be able to lay a hand on Maiza!
No... I was surprised myself as well.
いや 自分でも驚きましたよ
Congratulations, Firo.
おめでとう フイ一ロ
マイザ一さん…
Mr. Maiza.
ああ 腕?
Your arm...
You sure have developed your skills.
成長したのう !
長年 立会人をやつておるが
I've been doing these matches for a long time,
but you are the first candidate executive to win against Maiza.
マイ ザ一に勝つた幹部候補は
お前が初めてじゃ !
I won't say another word.
もう何も言ゎん
お前さんは
立派な力モツリス夕だよ フイ一ロ
You are a splendid Camorrista, Firo!
はい
Yes!
新しい幹部の誕生を祝って
私はここに祝砲を撃とう
Celebrating the appointment of our new executive, let me fire a salute!
おお一一つ
あはあ はぁはぁ はあん!
アイザツクが殺されたああああ !
Isaac was killed!
お嬢様は どち らです ?
Where is your little girl?
What happened?
どうなさいました?
連れていかれました川
She was taken away...
by those people in the white suits.
あの白い服の連中に
奴らは何者です?
Who are they?
I don't know.
分かり ません
彼らも私たちを
捜していたようですが
It seems they were looking for us as well, but...
娘だけを…
They only took my daughter...
お察しします
I'll keep a look out.
とりあえずは
我クの部屋に来て頂きましょうか
Let's have you come to our room for now.
ん? 失礼
Excuse me.
窓を開けたのは誰だ?
Who opened that window?!
A-A woman dressed in work clothes who sat over there...
そ そこに座っていた
作業着の女力ヾっ
A woman in work clothes?
作業着の女?
は はいつ 撃ち合いが始まつた時にっ
ま 窓を開けて外にっ
Yes!
When the shooting started, sh-she opened the window and went outside.
I-It's the truth!
ほ ほんとですつ !
同志グ一スからだ
作業着の女を捜せと
It's from comrade Goose.
He's telling us to look for a woman in work clothes.
作業着の女?
A woman in work clothes?
ちよ つ と様子を見てくる
I'll go take a look.
ここを頼む
Take care of things here.
ひつ
What's going on?
どうした?、 、
おい シヨ一ジはとこだ?
Hey. Where's George?
き ラ肖えた
H-He disappeared.
He disappeared!
消えたんだよ!
振り返ったら もういなかった!
When I looked back, he wasn't there anymore!
うう うう うゎあああああ
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
The Rail Tracer Covertly,
Repeatedly Slaughters Inside the Coaches
Miria, it's Rail Tracer!
Scary!
It says he's secretly murdering people!
That means he's moving around cautiously while killing everybody, right?!
You're amazing, Miria!
But what does this shanai (inside the train) part mean?
Scary!